Let's go to the squat position now and add the tubing into that.
Again, so many variations.
I'm going to show you something simple and basic.
I've got my feet about shoulder width apart, pretty much have to, to do a descent squat.
I'm going to take my tubing up, and I'm going to open up my palms so they're facing forward.
What am I doing with this?
As I go down and up in a squat position, I have to resist the tubing, right?
It's trying to keep me from coming up.
As I stretch the tubing straight up and down, it makes the squat harder.
Once again, you don't want to bend forward too much on this.
The key on this one, and something to keep in mind on this position, is this.
If you're tubing is really tight, you might not be able to get up unless your legs are close together.
A squat position, close together, doesn't work very well.
So the key on something like this, is that your tubing, what you've purchased, or what you have, has enough flexibility, that when you stand on it, you can really stand wide.
But it's definitely a great exercise, and I highly recommend it.